seekalyric.com 2016-11-01

# Privacy Policy at SeekaLyric.com

## SeekaLyric Privacy Policy

Privacy has become a major concern on the Internet. SeekaLyric.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This privacy statement describes how SeekaLyric.com deals with your information. By visiting SeekaLyric.com, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy statement.

Personal Information

SeekaLyric.com does not require you to disclose personal information anywhere on the site. However, SeekaLyric.com may offer additional features which require you to fill out forms requiring your personal information. We ask for your name, email address, city, country and birth date. The email address is used to send you a registration confirmation including activation link to active your account. The other personal details are used for display on your profile. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting patterns. Your IP address is also used to help diagnose technical problems. SeekaLyric.com does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third parties.

Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are used by many sites to store or transfer information between the main site and the computer you use to access the site. These cookies are stored in a special folder in your temporary internet files directory. SeekaLyric.com uses cookies in parts of the website. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. The advertisements may contain cookies. The advertisements are necessary to finance the costs of keeping this site online.

Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you are welcome to contact us.

Browse Artists
